For this lesson,
we will focus on solving memory overflow issues
and performance optimization.
Let's take a look.
Here, what's printed is the internal RAM
the total amount available,
and the currently available space.
This shows how the current idle space is like.
How is it printed?
Then, how do we address memory leaks, right?
For example, when we initialize
During Bluetooth initialization, we find a memory allocation error
What's going on?
Let's take a look at this
Let's see what's happening
Let's pull up these logs
Let's take a look at the log right now.
Let's check it out.
Here's the issue.
Let's see if it's the Bluetooth logo error.
Why is that?
Because when you see it print here,
It only has 19K of internal RAM left.
But the Bluetooth protocol stack takes up quite a bit of space.
We generally need around 780K or so.
How do we address this kind of issue?
Our internal RAM
Why does it get depleted so quickly?
How can we tackle this problem?
The detailed solution
Such as code configuration
Can be posted in the tech group.